Guide to the Blake Family Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Family correspondence, 1792-1921; Series II; 5; (12 boxes)
  - Select
    - Bushnell, George Ensign
      - Bushnell, George, 1862-1889 (Box 12, Folder 278)
      - Bushnell, Mary E., 1861-1874 (Box 12, Folder 279-281)
      - Bushnell, Mary E., 1875-1914 (Box 13, Folder 282-290)
      - Miscellaneous papers, 1865-1872 (Box 13, Folder 291-292)
    - Bushnell, Mary Elizabeth
      - Blake, Eli Whitney, 1853-1882 (Box 13, Folder 293-294)
      - Blake, Eliza M., 1907-1909 (Box 13, Folder 295-298)
      - Blake, Elizabeth, 1835-1865 (Box 13, Folder 299)
      - Blake, George A., 1835-1899 (Box 13, Folder 300-301)
      - Blake, Harriet, 1874-1905 (Box 13, Folder 302)
      - Blake, Henry Taylor, 1851-1909 (Box 14, Folder 303-304)
      - Blake, James D., 1858 (Box 14, Folder 305)
      - Bushnell, Dotha, 1876-1904 (Box 14, Folder 306-314)
      - Bushnell, George, 1865-1888 (Box 14, Folder 315-317)
      - Foster, Mary Anne, 1859 (Box 14, Folder 318)
      - Hazard, Ada, 1890-1897 (Box 14, Folder 319)
      - Hazard, Mary, 1876-1881 (Box 14, Folder 320)
      - Hershaw, Sarah, 1864 (Box 14, Folder 321)
      - MacWhorter, Henrietta, 1839-1899 (Box 14, Folder 322-324)
      - Merrill, Eliza, 1863-1905 (Box 14, Folder 325)
      - Osborne, Fanny Louisa, 1855-1886 (Box 15, Folder 326-329)
      - Parke, Jane, 1889 (Box 15, Folder 330)
      - Rice, Eliza, 1856-1901 (Box 15, Folder 331-335)
      - Miscellaneous papers, 1823-1916 (Box 15, Folder 336)
    - Hazard, Ada
      - Blake, Eli Whitney, 1876-1882 (Box 15, Folder 337)
      - Unidentified, 1868-1921 (Box 15, Folder 338-339)
    - Hazard, Caroline
      - Bushnell, Dotha, 1886-1908 (Box 15, Folder 340)
      - Hazard, Rowland Gibson, 1886-1897 (Box 15, Folder 341)
    - Hazard, Frederick Rowland: Rowland Hazard, 1880-1888 (Box 15, Folder 342)
    - Hazard, Margaret Anna: Rowland Gibson Hazard, 1868-1886 (Box 15, Folder 343-344)
    - Hazard, Mary Pierrepont
      - Bushnell, Dotha, 1872-1904 (Box 16, Folder 345)
      - Bushnell, George Ensign, 1870-1885 (Box 16, Folder 346)
      - Bushnell, Mary E., 1864-1904 (Box 16, Folder 347-348)
    - Hazard, Rowland
      - Bushnell, Dotha, 1904-1907 (Box 16, Folder 349)
      - Hazard, Rowland Gibson, 1875-1903 (Box 16, Folder 350)
    - Hazard, Rowland Gibson, 1862-1904 (Box 16, Folder 351-353)
    - Hazard, Thomas Pierrepont, 1903 (Box 16, Folder 354)
    - MacWhorter, Henrietta Whitney
      - Barstow, Elizabeth, 1840-1849 (Box 16, Folder 355)
      - Blake, Charles, 1878-1895 (Box 16, Folder 356)
      - Blake, Eli Whitney, 1839-1881 (Box 16, Folder 357)
      - Blake, Eliza M., 1839-1874 (Box 16, Folder 358)
      - Blake, George, 1859-1866 (Box 16, Folder 359)
      - Bushnell, Mary E., 1835-1896 (Box 16, Folder 360-361)
      - Osborne, Fanny Louisa, 1851-1891 (Box 16, Folder 362)
      - Rice, Eliza, 1865-1896 (Box 16, Folder 363)
    - Osborne, Fanny Louisa
      - Blake, Eli Whitney, 1847-1877 (Box 17, Folder 364)
      - Blake, Eli Whitney, Jr., 1846-1877 (Box 17, Folder 365)
      - Blake, Eliza, 1852-1857 (Box 17, Folder 366)
      - Blake, George, 1847-1880 (Box 17, Folder 367)
      - Bushnell, Mary E., 1847-1890 (Box 17, Folder 368)
      - MacWhorter, Henrietta Whitney, 1888-1890 (Box 17, Folder 369)
      - Osborne, Thomas, 1890 (Box 17, Folder 370)
      - Rice, Eliza, 1877-1886 (Box 17, Folder 371)
    - Osborne, Thomas Burr, 1874 (Box 17, Folder 372)
    - Rice, Eliza
      - Blake, Edward Foster, 1858-1862 (Box 17, Folder 373)
      - Blake, Eli Whitney, 1852-1884 (Box 17, Folder 374-378)
      - Blake, Eliza, 1857-1860 (Box 17, Folder 379)
      - Blake, George, 1873-1879 (Box 17, Folder 380-381)
      - Blake, Henry Taylor, 1893-1896 (Box 17, Folder 382)
      - Bushnell, Dotha, 1898-1904 (Box 17, Folder 383)
      - Bushnell, Mary E., 1862-1904 (Box 18, Folder 384-395)
      - MacWhorter, Henrietta Whitney, 1874-1896 (Box 18, Folder 396-397)
      - Osborne, Fanny Louisa, 1864-1894 (Box 19, Folder 398)
      - Rice, John, 1869-1896 (Box 19, Folder 399)
      - Seeley, Edward, 1873-1891 (Box 19, Folder 400)
    - Whitney, Eli
      - Blake, Eli Whitney, 1811-1818 (Box 19, Folder 401)
      - Miller, James, 1792-1823 (Box 19, Folder 402)
      - Whitney, Josiah, 1795 (Box 19, Folder 403)
      - Financial papers, 1807-1824 (Box 19, Folder 404)
    - Miscellaneous papers, undated (Box 19, Folder 405-408)
- Personal papers, 1780-1920; Series III; 1.75; (4 boxes)
  This series is arranged in two sections: Select and Topical. Select files are arranged alphabetically by the individual's name. Topical files contain material organized by record type.
  - Select
    - Blake, Edward Foster, 1852-1856 (Box 20, Folder 409)
    - Blake, Eliza Maria O'Brien, 1814-1819, 1845 (Box 20, Folder 410)
    - Blake, James Kingsley, 1870-1887 (Box 20, Folder 411)
    - Bushnell, Dotha, 1910-1914 (Box 20, Folder 412)
    - Bushnell, George, 1852-1891, 1848-1896 (Box 20, Folder 413-414)
    - Bushnell, Mary E. Blake, 1895-1912 (Box 21, Folder 415)
      - Oversize (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Cushing, Caleb, 1864 (Box 21, Folder 416)
    - McWhorter, Alexander, undated (Box 21, Folder 417)
    - McWhorter, Henrietta Whitney, 1841, undated (Box 21, Folder 418)
    - Unidentified, 1780's (Box 21, Folder 419)
  - Topical
    - Essays and poems, undated (Box 22, Folder 420)
    - Estate records, undated (Box 22, Folder 421)
    - Miscellaneous, 1832-1920 (Box 22, Folder 422-436)
      - Oversize (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Printed material, 1837-1910, undated (Box 23, Folder 437-451)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 23, Folder 452)
    - Obituaries, undated (Box 23, Folder 453)